What could go wrong?
Vacation is a comedy, adventure film directed by John Francis Daley.
Hoping to bring his family closer together and to recreate his childhood vacation for his own kids, a grown up Rusty Griswold
takes his wife and their two sons on a cross-country road trip to the coolest theme park in America, Walley World.
Needless to say, things don't go quite as planned.
Rusty Griswold, played by Ed Helms.
Debbie Griswold, played by Christina Applegate.
James Griswold, played by Skyler Gisondo.
Kevin Griswold, played by Steele Stebbins.
Stone Crandall, played by Chris Hemsworth.
Audrey Griswold, played by Leslie Mann.
Vacation is a 2015 American comedy road movie, written and
directed by John Francis Daley and Jonathan Goldstein.
It stars Ed Helms, Christina Applegate, Leslie Mann, Beverly
D'Angelo, Chris Hemsworth, and Chevy Chase.
It is the fifth theatrical installment of the Vacation film series.
Vacation was released on July 29, 2015, by Warner Bros.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics and
grossed $107 million on a $31 million budget.
The film explores themes of route 66, vacation, grand
canyon, dysfunctional family, road trip.
The tone is lighthearted.